cchubnigeria.com 2017-11-29

# Privacy Policy | Co-Creation Hub Nigeria

We care about your privacy. This Privacy Policy will tell you what information we collect; how we collect it, how we use it, how we disclose it, how we protect it, and what choices you have with respect to all of the above. We urge you to read this Privacy Policy so that you will understand both our commitment to you and your privacy, and how you can participate in that commitment.

This privacy policy governs the collection, storage and use of personal data collected by us, CcHub. It provides you with details about the personal data we collect from you, how we use your personal data and your rights to control personal data we hold about you. Please read this privacy policy carefully – by accessing or browsing this website and network (the “Services”), you confirm that you have read, understood and agree to this privacy policy in its entirety. If you do not agree to this privacy policy in its entirety, you must not use the Services. This privacy policy was last updated on 1st June 2012. Please check back regularly to keep informed of updates to this privacy policy.

* * *

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it regularly. If we make changes to this Privacy Policy, we will post the revised Privacy Policy on the Web Site and other places we deem appropriate. All such changes shall be binding on you 30 days after they are initially posted on the Web Site unless you are a new user, in which case they are binding on you immediately.

* * *

a. General. In general, you can browse the Web Site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. However, if you wish to become a member or use any of the services offered by the Web Site, you may be required to disclose certain information to us. You always have the option to not provide information by choosing not to become a member or use a particular service or feature. The Company is the sole owner of the information collected on the Web Site.

b. Registration. In order to use services offered by this Web Site, you may be required to first create an account with us. During the account set-up process, you are required to give certain contact information, including but not limited to your name, email address, mobile number, gender, age, city and skill sets. We use this information to contact you about the membership and services on our site in which you have expressed interest, and, the case of your approximate age, to determine whether you old enough to use the Web Site. You may have the option to provide additional information such as skill set, project and portfolio experience to us; we encourage you to submit this information so we can evaluate you membership status thoroughly. Where possible, we indicate which fields are required and which fields are optional.

c. Membership. If you register as a member on our Web Site, we may request certain personally identifiable information from you on our membership form. You must provide correct contact information (such as name, email, and mobile number) and a recent digital passport size photo which is a true representation of yourself. We use this information to evaluate and notify you of your membership status.

d. Surveys or Contests. From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on the Web Site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and email address), and demographic information. We use this information to notify contest winners and to award prizes. We may use a third party service provider to conduct these surveys or contests.

e. Log Files. As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do not link this automatically collected data to personally identifiable information.

f. Cookies. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site, unless you have elected to have the Web Site “remember” you, in which case the cookie will be linked to your user name. We may use both session ID cookies and/or persistent cookies. We use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file. We set a persistent cookie to store your password, so you don’t have to enter it more than once. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by this Web Site only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers or third parties. See the sections on “Third Party Advertisers” and “Co-Branded Pages” below. We may also use a third-party tracking service that uses cookies to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate. We do not control the use of cookies by third parties.

g. Correspondence. If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the Web Site, we may collect such information into a file specific to you.

* * *

a. Generally. We use your personal information to evaluate your membership status and to facilitate the services you request from us. We use your personal information in the file we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the Web Site to: inform you about job opportunities and openings, events, competitions, forums and any other technology related activities and enforce our Terms and Conditions of Use. We may compare and review your personal information for errors, omissions and for accuracy.

b. Communications from Us.

i. Newsletters. If you wish to subscribe to our newsletters, we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, you have the option to unsubscribe from receiving some or all of the newsletters. Please see the “Choice and Opt-out” section.

ii. Service-related Announcements. We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account.

iii. Customer Service. Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account.

c. Profile. We store information that we collect through your stated preferences, cookies, log files to create a “profile” of your preferences. We tie your personally identifiable information, and your activity history, to information in the profile, in order to improve the content of the site for you. We do not share your profile with other third parties, other than in aggregate, de-identified form.

* * *

a. Generally. As a matter of policy, we do not sell or rent any of your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without first providing you with an opportunity to opt-out. However, the following describes some of the ways that we may disclose your personal information in the normal course of providing our services.

b. Your Use of the Web Site. If you participate in a job board, bulletin board or other public forum offered by the Web Site, your User ID will be displayed on any content that you post and will therefore be available to the public. Therefore, if you associate your name with your User ID, your name will be available to the public. Any other information about yourself that you include in such posts will be publicly available.

c. Legal Requests. We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web Site.

d. Disclaimer. We cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personal information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose personal information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the Web Site.

* * *

We provide you the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information. For example, if you no longer wish to receive our newsletters, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at info@cchubnigeria.com. You may also update your preferences at any time by accessing our member information area. You will be notified before your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party.

* * *

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by these Web Site. The Web Site contain links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by us. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware of when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.

* * *

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire some or all of our services, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by making the change on our account information pages or by emailing us at info@cchubnigeria.com.

* * *

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information on our registration forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us from unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction, both during transmission and once we receive it.

* * *

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at info@cchubnigeria.com
